Cui Kaiyi: So this is the Open Day.
Is this for real?
Sun Qimeng: Is this for real?
Cui Kaiyi: A "real" or "fake" person?
Cui Kaiyi: Could it even be a "fake"?
Liang Renfang: Is it real or fake?
Time for the English Corner.
Liang Xiaoyu: Good morning, Maria.
Cui Kaiyi: Speaking English again.
Liang Xiaoyu: So many English Corners.
Liang Xiaoyu: I remember this one time,
Liang Xiaoyu: it was right by the stairs.
Liang Xiaoyu: Just English Corner nonstop.
Cui Kaiyi: Because I watched last episode.
Cui Kaiyi: They aired this last episode.
Cui Kaiyi: I laughed like crazy.
Cui Kaiyi: Speaking English inside,
Cui Kaiyi: and then I suddenly walked in.
Cui Kaiyi: Walked in like an NPC and said,
Cui Kaiyi: "If you two wanna speak English,
Cui Kaiyi: take it outside."
Let's go.
Sit properly.
Cui Kaiyi: Wow, Zhao Xilun is something.
Cui Kaiyi: He sat with Chen Hewen.
Sitting at this desk again.
Cui Kaiyi: Where does Yueer sit?
Cui Kaiyi: Excuse me?
Sun Qimeng: So that's how it is.
Cui Kaiyi: That's what I was wondering.
Sun Qimeng: This is hilarious.
Class dismissed.
The teacher is here.
Wow.
Sun Qimeng: You act like you're at home.
Cui Kaiyi: I have the same hair today.
Sit. Your class did pretty well on the test.
You, stand up.
Let me ask you a question.
Teacher.
Sun Qimeng: Right, this scene is so funny.
Cui Kaiyi: What?
Sun Qimeng: She made him change seats.
Teacher: Liang Renfang, don't move him.
You're probably a lost cause.
Come here.
Let's change his seat.
So scary.
Next question.
What genre is Dream of the Red Chamber?
A chaptered novel.
Ah.
Liang Xiaoyu: She was so scary coming in.
Cui Kaiyi: Felt like I was back in class.
Cui Kaiyi: Afraid she would call on me.
Cui Kaiyi: Whenever she asked a question,
Cui Kaiyi: I'd think about the answer.
Cui Kaiyi: Afraid of getting called on.
Sun Qimeng: Me too.
Sun Qimeng: I was so scared.
Liang Renfang: Me too.
Liang Xiaoyu: Is there food in her teeth?
Being naughty, aren't you?
Come on. You two are messing around.
Messing around here.
Come. No messing around under my watch.
Liang Xiaoyu: We aren't messing around.
Liang Xiaoyu: Just reminding you.
These two are good students.
Expressive.
Sun Qimeng: He's perfect for a time-out.
Sun Qimeng: I'm sorry.
Cui Kaiyi: Suited to sit by the teacher.
Cui Kaiyi: Two "bodyguard spots".
Cui Kaiyi: One is Chen Hewen,
Cui Kaiyi: And one is Zhao Xilun.
Oh my god.
Sun Qimeng: There's a new student.
There's a new student.
They're here, class.
Liang Xiaoyu: Teacher Du is here.
Liang Xiaoyu: I know this guest.
Hello, Teacher.
Where are you going?
What were we doing upstairs?
Everyone's in class. How is this...
How were the seats assigned?
Who are you sitting with? I'm with Yueer.
Then Yueer, come over here.
Liang Xiaoyu: Teacher Du thought he saw it.
Liang Renfang: Both are so confused.
I have two desk mates.
Liang Xiaoyu: Teacher Du is panicking.
Liang Xiaoyu: Two desk mates?
Liang Renfang: There's a story here.
Liang Renfang: A baffling story.
Hello, Teacher. My name is Hewen.
I am the Vice Class Monitor.
Liang Xiaoyu: Really.
Liang Xiaoyu: He thinks really fast.
He gave himself that title.
Cui Kaiyi: He's an officer.
Cui Kaiyi: What is he thinking?
Two of those stick figures radiate fire.
Cui Kaiyi: He just asked bluntly.
Cui Kaiyi: Teacher Haitao.
Maybe it's the two of us.
Hello, teacher.
What's your position?
Cui Kaiyi: And a boomerang.
Liang Renfang: So sudden.
Cui Kaiyi: Stick figure is an inside joke.
Cui Kaiyi: Because before, I forgot who,
Cui Kaiyi: asked me if I could draw.
Cui Kaiyi: I think it was Cao Yiheng.
Cui Kaiyi: Because he draws really well.
Liang Xiaoyu: You only draw stick figures?
Cui Kaiyi: Yeah, only stick figures.
Liang Xiaoyu: I remember now.
Cui Kaiyi: Because I can't draw at all.
Cui Kaiyi: Said I only draw stick figures.
Liang Xiaoyu: I ship it.
Sun Qimeng: Yes, so sweet.
Liang Renfang: Remembering small details.
Cui Kaiyi: And having two stick figures,
Cui Kaiyi: meaning the two of us,
Cui Kaiyi: I was quite surprised.
Cui Kaiyi: Because Cao Yiheng previously,
Cui Kaiyi: when it was just the two of us,
Cui Kaiyi: he would express a lot.
Cui Kaiyi: Whether it was, like,
Cui Kaiyi: super sweet words or direct ones.
Liang Xiaoyu: It's public this time.
Cui Kaiyi: First time in front of a crowd.
Cui Kaiyi: expressing things so obviously.
Sun Qimeng: Indeed.
Cui Kaiyi: Getting braver, deserves praise.
Cui Kaiyi: Alright, let's keep watching.
Did they hug right after he pushed them?
Yes.
Aww.
Sun Qimeng: Kaiyi, you look so confident.
Cui Kaiyi: Waiting with hands behind back.
Here they come, all prepared.
Sun Qimeng: Waiting.
Liang Xiaoyu: Here it comes!
Go, go.
Liang Renfang: Like a wedding send-off.
Liang Renfang: Like watching a wedding.
Cui Kaiyi: It's like...
Cui Kaiyi: It's like everyone is...
Cui Kaiyi: Everyone is sending blessings.
Cui Kaiyi: It's a heartwarming feeling.
Cui Kaiyi: I don't know why.
Sun Qimeng: It does feel like a wedding.
Sun Qimeng: Like the groom entering.
Liang Renfang: He almost walked right past.
Liang Renfang: Congrats to the newlyweds.
Cui Kaiyi: Is that how it was?
Cui Kaiyi: I saw it a bit differently.
Liang Renfang: That's so sweet!
Cui Kaiyi: I was quite nervous watching him.
Cui Kaiyi: Because I felt he'd probably
Cui Kaiyi: end up walking over to me.
Cui Kaiyi: Kept my hands behind my back,
Liang Renfang: ready for a hug.
Cui Kaiyi: Yeah, I was a little bit excited,
Cui Kaiyi: but mostly nervous.
Cui Kaiyi: Didn't know how he'd walk over.
Liang Xiaoyu: Worried he'd walk crookedly?
Cui Kaiyi: I wasn't that worried then.
Cui Kaiyi: Because I felt like he
Liang Renfang: would definitely walk over.
Cui Kaiyi: His sense of direction is good.
Cui Kaiyi: He probably wouldn't go wrong.
Liang Xiaoyu: It feels like one of those
Liang Xiaoyu: idol drama iconic scenes.
Cui Kaiyi: He really looks handsome in this.
Cui Kaiyi: Because when he took it off, I saw
Cui Kaiyi: his jawline right here.
Cui Kaiyi: The angle was just like this.
Cui Kaiyi: It wasn't straight on.
Cui Kaiyi: It felt quite different.
Cui Kaiyi: He looked really handsome.
Liang Xiaoyu: Your turn! Your turn, Meng!
Liang Renfang: Pushing her to other girls.
Liang Xiaoyu: Right.
Liang Xiaoyu: I can still reach her!
Cui Kaiyi: Fighting over Sun Qimeng.
Cui Kaiyi: Why not push her toward me?
Hug the person facing you! Come on!
Alright, come on, let's go.
Liang Xiaoyu: I've got goosebumps.
Liang Renfang: I'm so moved.
Let's have a hug.
Give me a hug.
Sun Qimeng: Sorry.
Cui Kaiyi: The soundtrack helps too.
Sun Qimeng: Yeah, indeed.
Sun Qimeng: Actually, I wanted to say...
Sun Qimeng: ...that back then...
Sun Qimeng: ...well...
Sun Qimeng: ...because when I stepped forward...
Sun Qimeng: ...and then...
Sun Qimeng: Liang Renfang said, "Come."
Sun Qimeng: "Come to me."
Sun Qimeng: Pushed behind every girl...
Sun Qimeng: ...they all...
Sun Qimeng: ...talked to me.
Sun Qimeng: Our girls are so wonderful.
Sun Qimeng: One day, we were chatting...
Sun Qimeng: ...outside the show.
Sun Qimeng: And I was recalling this scene.
Sun Qimeng: I could really hear clearly...
Sun Qimeng: Wu Xingying talking behind me.
Sun Qimeng: We were reminiscing, saying...
Sun Qimeng: My tears were welling up then.
Sun Qimeng: She said her tears welled up.
Sun Qimeng: Yeah, I was really super touched.
Cui Kaiyi: Plus, you were blindfolded then.
Cui Kaiyi: So your hearing was sharper.
Sun Qimeng: Yeah, I was really super touched.
Sun Qimeng: When you guys talked to me...
Sun Qimeng: ...I felt as if my bravery then...
Sun Qimeng: ...was given by every girl.
Sun Qimeng: I just felt I wasn't alone then.
Sun Qimeng: It really felt like that.
Sun Qimeng: It was so great.
Cui Kaiyi: Rooting for your happiness.
Cui Kaiyi: We hope you can be happy.
Sun Qimeng: It's just now, all of a sudden...
Sun Qimeng: ...this brings back feelings.
Cui Kaiyi: It happens.
Cui Kaiyi: Seeing this...
Liang Xiaoyu: The sparks are a bit strong.
Sun Qimeng: Yeah
Liang Xiaoyu: You've got long arms, kid
Liang Xiaoyu: You just intercepted it
Sun Qimeng: Why are they so shippable
Cui Kaiyi: This is good
Cui Kaiyi: I shipped it right then
Sun Qimeng: So blissful
Cui Kaiyi: You'd bump into Wu Xingying.
Sun Qimeng: That's too funny
Cui Kaiyi: Keep watching
Cui Kaiyi: Didn't know her foot was hurt.
Liang Renfang: Enduring it the whole time.
Cui Kaiyi: Only knew after you came down.
Liang Xiaoyu: It must've hurt a lot
Liang Renfang: I thought it was fine.
Liang Renfang: Then it hurt more and more
Liang Renfang: Then my foot felt sticky.
Liang Renfang: It was already bleeding
Cui Kaiyi: Just thinking about it now hurts
Liang Renfang: But it wasn't so bad then.
Cui Kaiyi: This episode is shipper heaven.
Cui Kaiyi: Love to see it.
Liang Renfang: I just knew
Liang Renfang: everyone would follow this
Liang Renfang: route.
Cui Kaiyi: You probably guessed it.
Liang Renfang: Yeah, I could guess it.
Liang Renfang: But I really didn't know,
Liang Renfang: what if we strayed off the path?
Liang Renfang: I wanted to walk a bit faster,
Liang Renfang: so that's why we bumped.
Liang Renfang: Just wanted to walk faster.
Liang Xiaoyu: You couldn't wait.
Liang Renfang: When we hugged, I was still a bit
Liang Renfang: unsure of the situation.
Liang Renfang: Hands up or down?
Liang Renfang: or to the left or the right.
Cui Kaiyi: Because both were blindfolded.
Liang Renfang: What's going on?
Liang Renfang: Right, had no idea.
Sun Qimeng: Was that your first hug?
Liang Renfang: Of course.
Sun Qimeng: Makes sense.
Liang Xiaoyu: Feeling his passionate gaze.
Cui Kaiyi: Cui Yihang is still waiting.
Cui Kaiyi: You're pretty good at this.
Cui Kaiyi: Cui Yihang.
Liang Xiaoyu: It really was...
Liang Xiaoyu: At the time, I was thinking,
Liang Xiaoyu: which way should I push?
Liang Xiaoyu: And then,
Liang Xiaoyu: I decided to pass the buck
Liang Xiaoyu: on to Cui Yihang.
Cui Kaiyi: You gave it to Cui Yihang.
Liang Xiaoyu: Right.
Liang Xiaoyu: Leave it to Cui Yihang.
Sun Qimeng: Being modest.
Sun Qimeng: You push.
All: You push Cui Yihang.
Cui Kaiyi: You're too funny.
Sun Qimeng: Cui Yihang.
Sun Qimeng: That's too funny.
What do you mean?
Cui Kaiyi: Missed each other.
Liang Renfang: I thought they'd meet.
Liang Renfang: Wouldn't they just turn around
Liang Renfang: and come over and hug?
Cui Kaiyi: Everyone was setting them up.
Cui Kaiyi: Sadly, they missed each other.
Wen: Someone's here.
Cui Kaiyi: They hugged each other.
Liang Xiaoyu: Right.
Liang Xiaoyu: I think so.
Liang Xiaoyu: I remember it seemed like...
Liang Renfang: With (Teacher Haitao).
Sun Qimeng: That's too funny.
Cui Kaiyi: Why is this world so confusing?
Liang Xiaoyu: Special Award: no regrets.
And not being afraid of looking foolish.
I hope I can express everything I want to.
Cui Kaiyi: Chen Hewen stepped up first.
Cui Kaiyi: Like I said, a big brother.
Cui Kaiyi: And so,
Cui Kaiyi: at that time, I felt that
Cui Kaiyi: if Chen Hewen stood up there,
Cui Kaiyi: Sun Qimeng and I should go up,
Cui Kaiyi: to show our gratitude for him.
Liang Xiaoyu: Sha Yue'er is very brave.
Liang Xiaoyu: Since she went up first.
Liang Xiaoyu: The rest of us followed her.
Cui Kaiyi: Right.
Liang Xiaoyu: Right.
Cui Kaiyi: She encouraged us to go up too.
During the dinner,
I mentioned that
my mood was white.
Liang Xiaoyu: We were all stunned here.
Liang Xiaoyu: What does that mean?
You wore white the first day we met.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Liang Xiaoyu: The mystery is solved.
The first time I saw you at the dinner,
I felt you were grounded and confident.
Hope you find a match in the Signal House.
Liang Xiaoyu: I'm so touched.
Liang Xiaoyu: It really is me.
Liang Xiaoyu: Zhao Xilun's was something.
Cui Kaiyi: Zhao Xilun.
Liang Xiaoyu: Right.
Liang Xiaoyu: The first moment I noticed him
Liang Xiaoyu: was when he was at the table,
Liang Xiaoyu: sharing things with us.
Liang Xiaoyu: He shared his insights,
Liang Xiaoyu: and analyze the science.
Liang Xiaoyu: Then he'd explain his logic.
Liang Xiaoyu: I really admire him.
Liang Xiaoyu: He's a great little brother.
Cui Kaiyi: I can feel that.
Liang Xiaoyu: Yeah.
I really want to say this to Sun Qimeng.
Sun Qimeng.
You're a beautiful, poised, sunny girl.
Your energy has always been contagious,
and it always heals me.
Whether you're here or anywhere else,
I believe you'll be happy.
Let him
nothing
I know you're loving, but it's over.
It doesn't matter, but the
Cui Kaiyi: You really used it.
Sun Qimeng: I'm sorry.
Cui Kaiyi: Sorry for what?
Sun Qimeng: Liang Xiaoyu, you know when
Sun Qimeng: shouted out to me,
Sun Qimeng: I really felt
Sun Qimeng: My light in the Signal House.
Sun Qimeng: Really.
Sun Qimeng: We don't have to say anything,
Sun Qimeng: and you can just
Sun Qimeng: read my mind.
Cui Kaiyi: That power from Liang Xiaoyu,
Cui Kaiyi: we all felt it.
Cui Kaiyi: Not to mention Sun Qimeng.
Cui Kaiyi: Hearing that firsthand,
Cui Kaiyi: Liang Renfang and I were
Cui Kaiyi: so moved.
Liang Renfang: We could only keep nodding.
Sun Qimeng: My threshold for happiness
Sun Qimeng: is already quite low.
Sun Qimeng: I get happy very easily.
Sun Qimeng: But Liang Xiaoyu's arrival
Sun Qimeng: multiplied my happiness.
Sun Qimeng: From being in the dorm,
Sun Qimeng: I felt I wasn't alone anymore.
Sun Qimeng: We really have a great bond.
Sun Qimeng: And then,
Sun Qimeng: Liang Xiaoyu is like a sister.
Sun Qimeng: Call daily post Signal House.
Liang Xiaoyu: Sun Qimeng is my kind of,
Liang Xiaoyu: A home-invasion kind of love.
Liang Xiaoyu: You know?
Sun Qimeng: Really, because I'd always...
Sun Qimeng: I asked if we could call.
Liang Xiaoyu: Sometimes I'm still asleep.
Liang Xiaoyu: And then
Liang Xiaoyu: Sun Qimeng would call.
Sun Qimeng: Right.
Cui Kaiyi: Whatcha doing, Liang Xiaoyu?
Sun Qimeng: She told me that she...
Sun Qimeng: She doesn't call anyone else.
Sun Qimeng: She only calls me.
Liang Xiaoyu: But when someone calls me,
Liang Xiaoyu: I feel very happy.
Sun Qimeng: Thank you.
Sun Qimeng: I was even happier later on.
Sun Qimeng: You really became My light.
Sun Qimeng: And then later,
Sun Qimeng: Wu Xingying came.
Sun Qimeng: I felt
Sun Qimeng: so happy!
Sun Qimeng: Because at the time I thought,
Sun Qimeng: I really like Wu Xingying.
Sun Qimeng: And then
Sun Qimeng: we didn't become roommates.
Sun Qimeng: Wu Xingying became a roommate.
Sun Qimeng: I felt so happy I could faint.
Liang Renfang: Everything's perfect now.
Sun Qimeng: Really.
Sun Qimeng: And I feel like everyone is so nice.
Sun Qimeng: The guys are great too.
Sun Qimeng: I definitely have to say this.
Sun Qimeng: Really.
Sun Qimeng: Everyone is super nice.
Liang Xiaoyu: I remember last time we...
Liang Xiaoyu: There was this one time
Liang Xiaoyu: on that sofa.
Liang Xiaoyu: We were chatting together,
Liang Xiaoyu: talking about catchphrases.
Liang Xiaoyu: And at the time I said,
Liang Xiaoyu: I asked Sun Qimeng,
Liang Xiaoyu: "Guess my catchphrase?"
Sun Qimeng: I'll repeat it right now.
Sun Qimeng: She just says,
Sun Qimeng: she's like this every day.
Sun Qimeng: It's really like this.
Liang Xiaoyu: The catchphrase is,
She's touching you, really.
Mengmeng.
Sun Qimeng: Yeah, it's really like this.
Liang Xiaoyu: I just think what's especially
Liang Xiaoyu: touching about Sun Qimeng is
Liang Xiaoyu: that no matter what she goes through,
Liang Xiaoyu: she can always stay so cheerful.
Cui Kaiyi: And still smiling!
Sun Qimeng: Hugs!
Cui Kaiyi: Quick,
Cui Kaiyi: you two hug first, in this...
Cui Kaiyi: in this time and space,
Cui Kaiyi: at this place.
Cui Kaiyi: So happy!
Cui Kaiyi: Stand up!
Sun Qimeng: Let's hug!
Liang Xiaoyu: Sit.
Cui Kaiyi: I really feel that
Cui Kaiyi: in the Signal House, apart from
Cui Kaiyi: love,
Cui Kaiyi: friendship is more beautiful.
Liang Renfang: Yes.
Sun Qimeng: Yeah.
I feel very lucky
that
I met someone on the same wavelength.
And then,
It's okay.
You've got this,
Teacher Yu.
I hope we can go further together.
Yeah.
This is...
Oh my god.
Liang Renfang: It's okay, let's keep going.
Cui Kaiyi: I've figured out the thumbnail.
Cui Kaiyi: Just cut shots of you crying
Cui Kaiyi: and turn them into three clips.
Sun Qimeng: She looks so pretty crying.
Cui Kaiyi: Really, she is...
Sun Qimeng: Her eyes suddenly teared up.
Cui Kaiyi: She was holding them in.
Liang Renfang: I kept holding it back.
Liang Renfang: You know?
Cui Kaiyi: I always thought maybe he was...
Liang Renfang: Just a very chill kind of
Liang Renfang: "capybara".
Liang Renfang: He wouldn't get super mad.
Liang Renfang: Or get sad or show emotion.
Liang Renfang: But that day, I saw a lot.
Liang Renfang: It's just, slowly,
Liang Renfang: Seeing a new side of him.
Liang Renfang: And he's opening up more.
Liang Renfang: Okay, I'm good.
I hope everyone here
can embrace all the beautiful things.